<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Rust Changelogs</title><link>https://releases.rs/docs/unreleased/</link><description>Recent content on Rust Changelogs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://releases.rs/docs/unreleased/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://releases.rs/docs/unreleased/1.66.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases.rs/docs/unreleased/1.66.0/</guid><description> 1.66.0 # Unreleased
Will be stable on: 15 December, 2022 Will branch from master on: 28 October, 2022 Neither require nor imply lifetime bounds on opaque type for well formedness Fix #[derive(Default)] on a generic #[default] enum adding unnecessary Default bounds Stabilize #![feature(mixed_integer_ops)] Bump Unicode to version 15.0.0, regenerate tables Make the c feature for compiler-builtins an explicit opt-in Update unicode-rs crates to Unicode 15 Stabilize bench_black_box</description></item><item><title/><link>https://releases.rs/docs/unreleased/1.65.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases.rs/docs/unreleased/1.65.0/</guid><description> 1.65.0 # Unreleased
Will be stable on: 3 November, 2022 Will branch from master on: 16 September, 2022 Tracking issue for RFC 2046, label-break-value Stabilize let else Use niche-filling optimization even when multiple variants have data. Stabilize const_ptr_offset_from. Stabilize generic associated types Uplift the let_underscore lints from clippy into rustc. Don&amp;rsquo;t derive PartialEq::ne. consider unnormalized types for implied bounds Update to LLVM 15 Do not allow Drop impl on foreign fundamental types Add armv4t-none-eabi take2 Stabilize std::io::read_to_string Stringify non-shorthand visibility correctly Update the minimum external LLVM to 13 Sunset RLS Don&amp;rsquo;t duplicate file descriptors into stdio fds Normalize struct field types in confirm_builtin_unsize_candidate</description></item></channel></rss>