<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Rust Changelogs</title><link>https://releases.rs/docs/unreleased/</link><description>Recent content on Rust Changelogs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://releases.rs/docs/unreleased/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://releases.rs/docs/unreleased/1.65.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases.rs/docs/unreleased/1.65.0/</guid><description>1.65.0 (3 November, 2022) # Language # Error on as casts of enums with #[non_exhaustive] variants Stabilize let else Stabilize generic associated types (GATs) Add lints let_underscore_drop, let_underscore_lock, and let_underscore_must_use from Clippy Stabilize breaking from arbitrary labeled blocks (&amp;ldquo;label-break-value&amp;rdquo;) Uninitialized integers, floats, and raw pointers are now considered immediate UB. Usage of MaybeUninit is the correct way to work with uninitialized memory. Stabilize raw-dylib for Windows x86_64, aarch64, and thumbv7a Do not allow Drop impl on foreign ADTs Compiler # Stabilize -Csplit-debuginfo on Linux Use niche-filling optimization even when multiple variants have data Associated type projections are now verified to be well-formed prior to resolving the underlying type Stringify non-shorthand visibility correctly Normalize struct field types when unsizing Update to LLVM 15 Fix aarch64 call abi to correctly zeroext when needed debuginfo: Generalize C++-like encoding for enums Add special_module_name lint Add support for generating unique profraw files by default when using -C instrument-coverage Allow dynamic linking for iOS/tvOS targets New targets:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://releases.rs/docs/unreleased/1.66.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases.rs/docs/unreleased/1.66.0/</guid><description>1.66.0 nightly # Unreleased, branched from master
Will be stable on: 15 December, 2022 Will branch from master on: 28 October, 2022 Do not consider repeated lifetime params for elision. (merged 2 days ago) Stabilize duration_checked_float (merged 7 days ago) Don&amp;rsquo;t link to libresolv in libstd on Darwin (merged 7 days ago) Update libstd&amp;rsquo;s libc to 0.2.135 (to make libstd no longer pull in libiconv.dylib on Darwin) (merged 7 days ago) Change process spawning to inherit the parent&amp;rsquo;s signal mask by default (merged 10 days ago) Stabilize proc_macro::Span::source_text (merged 11 days ago) Stabilize map_first_last (merged 20 days ago) Stabilize half_open_range_patterns (merged 21 days ago) Fix #[derive(Default)] on a generic #[default] enum adding unnecessary Default bounds (merged 28 days ago) Make the c feature for compiler-builtins an explicit opt-in (merged 32 days ago) Stabilize #!</description></item></channel></rss>